So I told Carl, nobody, no matter
how famous their parents are...
그래서 칼한테 그랬어
부모가 아무리 잘 나가도
...is allowed to climb
on the dinosaur.
공룡엔 못 올라간다고 말야
그래도 막무가내였지...
Of course, it went
right in one ear....
I love how he cares so much
about stuff.
저 진지한 모습
너무 멋져
If I squint, I can pretend
he's Alan Alda.
어떻게 보면
'알란 알다' 같기도 해
Oh, good. Another dinosaur story.
지겨워, 또 공룡 얘기야?
쟤들은 언제 멸종하지?
When are those gonna become extinct?
If I was a superhero who could fly
and be invisible...
하늘을 나는
투명인간 수퍼맨이 되면
... that would be the best.
정말 기분 째지겠다
What does Rachel see in this guy?
이런 녀석이 뭐가 좋다고?
사랑해, 레이첼
I love Rachel.
I wish she was my wife.
내 아내라면 좋겠다
누가 노랠 하지?
Who's singing?
The One With the Race Car Bed
어렸을 때 '해피 데이즈'
놀이하면 누구 맡았어?
When you guys were kids
and you played Happy Days...
...who were you?
I was Richie.
- 난 맨날 ' 리치 ' 했는데
- 난 맨날 ' 조니 '였어
I was always Joanie.
Question: Was "Egg the Gellers!"
the war cry of your neighborhood?
'겔러 남매 재수 없어! '가
너희 동네에서 나던 소리야?
- 침대의 왕 / 파격 세일
- '침대의 왕'이다!
It's the Mattress King!
Change the channel!
보지 마, 자기
채널 돌려!
Wait! I want to see this!
After I divorce him...
볼 거야, 이혼하고 나면
왕국의 반은 내 거라구
...half of that kingdom
is gonna be mine!
침대 왕국에 절망이 가득합니다
왕국의 왕비가 사라졌으니까요
Despair fills the mattress showroom.
My Kingdom is suddenly
without a Queen.
실의에 빠진 저는
사정없이...
I'm so depressed...
...I'm going to slash...
...my prices!
깎아드려요!
서두르세요!
Check it out!
599 for a California king!
킹사이즈 599달러
필로우 탑 퀸셋은 499달러!
499 for a pillow-top queen set!
중세 가격으로 드려요!
I'm going medieval on prices!
What a wank!
변태 아냐?
세상에! 물건 팔려고
이혼을 이용해먹다니!
I cannot believe he's using
our divorce to sell mattresses!
필로우 탑 퀸셋이 499달러인데
그깟 이혼이 대수야?
I know. At $499 for a pillow-top
queen, who cares about the divorce?
Those babies will sell themselves!
정말 불티나겠구만
알았으니까
그만 째려봐
And I'm appalled for you, by the way.
가까운 '침대의 왕'을
찾아주세요!
I'm close! I'm cheap! I'm the King!
네, 아빠
내일 같이 갈게요
Okay, Daddy. We'll see you
tomorrow night. Okay, bye-bye.
끊을게요
"We"?
같이?
are having dinner with my Dad
tomorrow night. I hope that's okay.
내일 아빠랑 저녁 먹을 건데
괜찮겠지?
Oh, shoot!
Tomorrow's not good.
내일은 좀 그래
I'm supposed to fall off
the Empire State Building...
엠파이어스테이트 빌딩에서
뛰어내리기로 선약이 돼있거든
...and land on a bicycle
with no seat, so....
아빤 자기 안 싫어하셔
My father doesn't hate you.
Please. He refers to me
as "Wet-Head."
'주접이'라고 하시는데도?
Honey, he calls everybody
by a nickname.
아빤 원래 별명만 부르셔
제발 부탁이야
하룻밤만 참아 줘
I know. Just one dinner.
One night. For me. Please?
아빠도 나만큼 자기를
좋아하게 해줄게
I just want him to love you like I do.
All right. Well, not exactly
like I do.
물론 나랑 같진 않겠지
But if you do come to dinner...
대신 같이 가주면 자기가
좋아하는 검은 속옷 입어줄게
...I'll love you like I do
in that black thing that you like.
I'll go.
내가 가지
Fine.
- 좋아
- 고마워
Thank you.
Hi, Gunther.
안녕하세요?
그래, 두고봐
Yeah. We'll see.
Hey, you guys!
얘들아!
안녕!
Guess what.
- 있잖아
- 왜?
일거리 땄어
-I got a gig!
-Great!
That's why I can never be an actor.
I can't say "gig."
저래서 난 배우 안 한다니까
저런 말 못 하겠더라
난 '크로와상'을 못해
I can't say "croissant."
Oh, my God!
말해버렸네
무슨 역인데?
-What's the part?
-It's not a part.
이번엔 직접 연기하는 게 아니라
드라마 연기를 가르치는 일이야
I'm teaching Acting for Soap Operas
at the Learning Extension.
Come on! That's great!
- 잘 됐다
- 맞아
It's my chance to give
something back...
배우 세계에 뭔가 공헌할
기회가 온 거지
...to the acting community.
You're probably not allowed to sleep
with your students.
학생하고 자는 건
금지 돼 있겠지?
알아
I know.
침대의 왕 가구점
I don't know, Monica.
It feels funny just being here.
여기 와있으니까
좀 찝찝해
If you buy a bed from
Janice's ex-husband...
재니스 전남편네서 침대를 사면
챈들러가 배신감 느낄 거야
...it's like betraying Chandler.
Not at these prices!
싸면 장땡이지
얘! 영국 같으면 이 차는
가게 뒤쪽에 가있을 텐데
You know, in England this car would be
on the other side of the store.
피비, 누워봐
Come here.
This is my new bed!
이걸로 살 거야
여기서 자면 꿀맛이겠어
You gotta feel this bad boy!
Monica, it still feels so weird,
you know?
모니카, 이래도 되는 거야?
챈들러는 네 친구잖아
Chandler's your friend.
Oh, my God!
이럴 수가!
All right, take this bed.
You can make other friends.
그냥 이거 사고
친구 새로 사귀어
Good evening.
반가워요
I am Mr. Tribbiani.
난 트리비아니예요
And I will be teaching
Acting for Soap Operas.
여러분께 드라마 연기를
강의할 겁니다
Now...
...on my first day as Dr. Drake
Ramoray on Days Of Our Lives...
'우리의 날들'의 라모레 박사를
처음 연기하던 날...
... I learned one of the most important
things in soap opera acting...
드라마 연기에서 가장
중요한 것 중 하나는...
...is reacting.
반응입니다
This does not mean acting again.
반만 응하란 뜻이 아녜요
It means you don't have a line,
but someone else just did.
대사가 없을 때라도
가만있지 말고 이렇게 하세요
And it goes something like this.
Thanks. Thanks a lot.
고마워요
미리 말해두겠는데
By the way, before I forget.
To work in soap operas...
드라마에 나오려면
외모에 신경들 좀 써야겠어요
...some of you will have to
become more attractive.
오늘은 여기까집니다
All right, moving right along....
- 안녕
- 왔어?
-How was teaching last night?
-Great! You get to say stuff like...
- 어제 수업은 어땠어?
- 좋았지
내가 이랬어 '종 쳤어도 수업을
끝내고 안 끝내고는 내 맘이야'
... "Hey, the bell doesn't dismiss you.
I dismiss you."
Oh, nice.
멋지다
Oh, and I got an audition
for All My Children!
거기다 '내 아이들'에
오디션도 보게 됐어
- 정말?
- 죽여주는 역이야
It's this great part.
닉이란 권투선수 역인데
볼 것도 없이 딱 나라니까
This boxer named Nick.
And I'm so, so right for it.
He's just like me.
권투선수에 못된 쌍둥이
형제가 있는 것만 빼면
Except that he's a boxer...
...and has an evil twin.
땀 따라람~
'침대의 왕'에서 배달입니다
Hear ye, hear ye!
Delivery from the Mattress King!
You Miss Geller?
겔러 양이세요?
- 네
- 사인하세요
Sign here.
중간 이름이 있던가?
Do I have a middle name?
All right. Monica "Felula"...
모니카 벌룰라...
겔러
...Geller.
It's that bedroom there.
침실은 저기예요
Monica bought a bed
from the Mattress King?
모니카가 '침대의 왕'에서
침대를 샀어?
응, 제발 제발
챈들러한텐 비밀이야
Please, please, please
don't say anything to Chandler.
챈들러한테 거짓말하라고?
-You want me to lie to him?
-ls that a problem?
- 힘들겠어?
- 아니
Oh, hey, "Nick the boxer."
Let's see what you got!
권투선수 닉!
실력 좀 보여줘
덤벼봐
All right, put them up.
Hey, you're pretty good at this.
너 정말... 제법인데
YWCA할 때 주님을 제대로
안 섬기는 녀석들 때문에 배웠지
I had to learn.
I was staying at the "Y"...
...and some of the young men
weren't acting Christian enough.
야아!
Hey, now!
And I'm bleeding.
Okay, great.
피나잖아
잘 했다
Wow! And I'm a vegetarian!
난 채식주의자인데
미안해, 얼음찜질 좀 하자
머리 뒤로 젖혀
I'm sorry.
We'll put some ice on it.
Put your head back.
알았어
-I can't see.
-I have you.
- 눈이 안 보여
- 나만 따라와
Oh, God!
Which bedroom do you want it in,
Ms. Geller?
어느 방으로 들여갈까요
겔러 양?
창 쪽에 더럽게
깨끗한 방 있죠?
It's the compulsively neat one
by the window.
알겠습니다
Gotcha.
아빠!
Hi, Daddy!
This is where they put us?
자리가 여기야?
What? There was no table
in the kitchen?
주방엔 남는 자리가
없나보지?
- 잘 있었니?
- 로스 기억하시죠?
-Hello, baby.
-You remember Ross.
오랜만입니다, 그린 박사님
Nice to see you again, Dr. Greene.
So!
그래...
-How's the library?
-Museum.
- 도서관은 어떤가?
- 박물관입니다
-What happened to the library?
-There never was a library.
- 도서관은 어쩌고?
- 도서관은 아닙니다
I mean, there are libraries.
It's just...
그 많은 도서관 중에
제가 일해본 곳은 없단 뜻이죠
...that I've never worked at one.
이 집은 바닷가재를 잘 하지
You know what's really good here?
The lobster.
-Shall I just order three?
-lf you're really hungry.
- 그걸로 3인분 시킬까?
- 정말 배고프신가봐요
It was a joke. I made a joke.
그냥 농담한 거예요
Actually, Daddy,
Ross is allergic to lobster.
로스가 바닷가재를
못 먹거든요
도서관에서 일하는 사람은
바닷가재도 못 먹나보군
Who's allergic to lobster? I guess
someone that works in a library.
-It's
-I know. It's a museum!
- 도서관이 아니라...
- 알아, 박물관!
You're the only who can make a joke?
At least mine was funny.
자네만 농담하나?
내 건 재밌기나 하지
Waiter.
웨이터!
We will have two lobsters
and a menu.
바닷가재 둘이랑
메뉴판 좀 갖다줘요
So, Dr. Greene, how's the old boat?
박사님, 보트는 어때요?
녹슬었어, 보트가
녹슬면 어떤지 아나?
They found rust. Do you know
what rust does to a boat?
Gives it a nice antique-y look?
골동품 같을까요?
Rust is boat cancer, Ross.
녹은 배의 암이나
다름없다네, 로스
Wow, I'm sorry.
안 됐네요, 전 어릴 때
암으로 자전거를 잃었죠
When I was a kid,
I lost a bike to that.
Excuse me for a moment.
잠깐 실례하겠네, 가기 전에
레빈 부부한테 인사나 해야지
I want to say good night
to the Levines before we go.
그러세요!
Honey, stop. It's not that bad.
왜 그래?
잘 하고 있어
그래
Your dad must have added wrong.
He only tipped 4%.
계산을 잘못하셨나봐
팁이 4%밖에 안돼
Yeah. That's Daddy.
- 아빤 원래 그래
- 뭐가 어째?
"That's Daddy"? Doesn't it
bother you? You're a waitress.
너도 웨이트리스면서
열 안 받아?
물론 열 받지
Yes, it bothers me.
내 손님이 그러면
차에다 침 뱉어서 갖다주지
If he was a regular at the coffee
house, I'd be serving him sneezers.
- 그럼...
- 그럼 뭐?
-So?
-So, Ross...
나도 수없이 얘기해봤지만
소용없어
... I've bugged him about this
a million times. He won't change.
Do you really serve people sneezers?
정말 침 뱉은 차도 갖다줘?
Well, I don't.
난 아니지
All right, kids. Ready?
- 이제 일어나지
- 감사합니다, 박사님
Thanks again, Dr. Greene.
아니야
Wait, I think I forgot my receipt.
잠깐!
계산서를 깜빡했네
- 그냥 가세요
- 왜 그래?
-You don't need that.
-Why not?
먹지가 몸에 안 좋대요
자꾸 만지시면...
The carbon. It's messy. I mean,
gets on your fingers and causes...
야맹증이 생기거든요
... night blindness.
이게 뭐야?
What is this?
Who put a 20 down here?
20달러는 뭐지?
Oh, yeah, that would be me.
제가 그랬어요
제가 원래...
I have a problem.
팁을 팍팍 써야 직성이
풀려서요, 병적이죠
I tip way too much.
Way too much.
-It's a sickness, really.
-Yeah, it is.
정말 그래요
너무 심한 거 아냐?
-We have to do something about that.
-Excuse me.
잠깐만
내가 짠돌이 같나?
You think I'm cheap?
He didn't mean anything by that.
He really didn't.
아빠, 별 뜻 없었어요
정말이에요
아무 뜻 없었어요
Nothing I do means anything. Really.
This is nice.
I pay $200 for dinner.
멋지구만, 200달러 낸 사람도
있는데 20달러에 큰손 되고 말야
You put down $20 and you come out
looking like Mr. Big Shot.
You really want to be Mr. Big Shot?
Here.
진짜 큰손 돼볼 텐가?
그럼 이렇게 해
전부 내고 큰손 하라구
I'll tell you what. You pay the
whole bill, Mr. Big Shot. All right?
Well, "Mr. Big Shot" is better
than "Wet-Head."
큰손이 주접이보단 낫네
Okay, some tricks of the trade.
몇 가지 요령이 있어요
Now, I've never been able to cry
as an actor...
저도 처음엔 울지를 못했죠
그래서 울어야 될 장면에선
...so if I have to cry...
... I cut a hole in my pocket...
주머니에 구멍을 내서
족집게를 넣고는
...take a pair of tweezers...
...and just start pulling.
있는 힘껏 꼬집어요
그럼 사악함을 표현하는
방법을 얘기해보죠
Or let's say I want to convey...
...that I've just done
something evil.
That would be your basic I've-got-a-
fish-hook-in-my-eyebrow-and-l-like-it.
낚시바늘로 눈썹을 끌어올린다
생각하세요, 이렇게 말이죠
나쁜 소식을 접하는
장면이라면
Let's say I've just gotten bad news.
Well, all I do there
is try and divide 232 by 13.
암산으로 232나누기 13을
하면 되죠
And that's how it's done.
이렇게 하는 거예요
다들 수고 많았어요
Great soap opera acting
tonight, everybody.
Class dismissed.
수업 끝!
Hey, Mr. Trib.
- 트리비아니 선생님
- 그래
Guess what? I got an audition!
저 있죠...
오디션 땄어요
내 학생이 오디션을?
너무 자랑스럽구나
One of my students got an audition.
I'm so proud!
I was wondering if you'd
coach me for it.
지도를 좀
부탁 드려도 될까요?
You bet! What's the part?
물론이지
어떤 역인데?
Oh, it's great!
끝내줘요, '내 아이들'의
권투선수 닉 역이죠
It's a role on All My Children.
Nick the boxer.
그냥 좀 넘어가지
꼭 그래야 했어?
You couldn't leave it alone.
Four percent, okay? I tip more than
that when there's a bug in my food.
4%라니? 음식에서 벌레가
나와도 그것보단 더 주겠다
아빠랑 좀 친해지라고
만든 자리라구
Tonight was about the two of you
getting along.
Would you just see
my chiropractor already?
아는 의사 소개시켜준다니까
I'm gonna go to a doctor who went
to medical school in a mini-mall.
그래, 돌팔이 의사한테
진찰 한번 받아볼까?
Hey, Pheebs. What are you doing?
피비, 뭐해?
안절부절못하는 거야
I'm freaking out!
Monica trusted me with something
and she shouldn't have!
모니카가 날 믿고...
그게 실수야!
I haven't lived here in a while,
so I have to ask you.
잊어버려서 그러는데
하나만 물을게
모니카가 아직도
방에 불을 켜니?
Does Monica still turn the lights on
in her room?
그럼
I am so dead!
난 죽었다
Look, here's the bottom line.
그럼 이렇게 해봐, 로스
서두르면 만회할 수 있어
This is fixable if we act fast, okay?
오전에 같이 식사하면서
점수 좀 따
I'll invite him to brunch tomorrow,
and you can make nice.
Honey, I have tried to make nice.
It doesn't work.
여태까지도 노력했는데
소용없었던 거야
아빠가 좀 까다로운 건
인정해
Look, I realize my father
is difficult.
But that's why you have got to be
the bigger man here.
그러니까 자기도 좀 더
대범하게 굴라구
대범하게 굴 수야 있지
Sweetie, I could be the bigger man.
I could be the biggest man.
근데 엄청나게 큰 거인처럼
군다고 해도 소용이 없는걸?
I could be a huge, giant man, and
it still wouldn't make a difference.
Except I could pick your father up and
say, "Like me! Like me, tiny doctor!"
이렇게라도 할까? '제발 절
좋아해 주세요, 꼬마 박사님'
Can't you just try it one more time?
For me? For me?
딱 한번만 더 시도해 줘
날 위해서!
One brunch is not gonna
solve anything.
밥 한 끼 먹는다고
해결될 것 같아?
이젠 인정하라구
우린 절대 안돼
Face it.
We're never gonna get along.
Well, you are just going to have to.
내가 이렇게
사정하는데도 못해?
우리 엄마 아빠 헤어지신
걸로도 부족해서
I've already got a mother and father
who cannot stay in the same room.
자기까지 잃으란 말야?
I don't want to have a separate room
for you too!
알았어
I'll get the bagels.
베이글 가져올게
What's this?
이게 뭐야?
너무 좋지?
Isn't it cool?
내가 주문한 거랑 다른데
This is not the bed I ordered.
알지, 상품으로
딴 건가보지?
I know! You must have won
a contest or something.
피비!
Why is this car in my bedroom?
이게 왜 여기 와 있어?
I'm sorry. I wasn't looking...
미안해, 내 실수야
...and the store won't take
it back, because you signed for it.
근데 벌써 사인을 해서
교환도 안 된대
-When did I sign for it?
-When I was you.
난 사인 안 했는데?
내가 했지, 다 조이 탓이야
코를 안 막더라구
It's all Joey's fault,
because he left his nose open!
Did you make brownies today?
혹시 빵 구웠니?
IKnock, knock!
똑똑!
Quick! Take off your dress.
He won't notice the bed.
빨리 옷 벗어서
침대 가려
I'm going for sushi.
Does anybody want?
초밥 먹으러 갈 건데
누구...
Somebody missed the off-ramp!
웬 차가 들어와 있냐?
모니카 침대야, 왜?
It's Monica's bed. What?
그래
It's a racecar!
경주차구나!
This has always been Monica's bed.
You just noticed?
원래부터 있던 건데
여태 몰랐어?
How self-involved are you?
친구한테 그렇게 무관심해?
새 침대도 아니라면서
비닐은 왜 씌워져 있는데?
If this bed isn't new, then how come
there's plastic on the mattress?
Sometimes I have bad dreams.
악몽을 꾸면 가끔 실수를...
Look...
이봐, 제일 친구가 링 위에서
쓰러져 가는 모습도 지켜봤어
... I just saw my best friend's
brain smeared across the canvas.
It's not gonna be me.
난 그렇게 되지 않아
절대로!
Not me.
와!
That was good.
정말 대단해
That was
Tweezers?
- 족집게?
- 아뇨
-That was really good.
-Thanks.
- 정말 잘해
- 고마워요
Any suggestions?
해주실 말씀은요?
게이 권투선수를
연기하라고 했다구?
You told him to play the boxer gay?
정확히 말하자면...
수퍼 게이였지
I might have said...
... "super-gay."
망치려고 작정했구만
You totally screwed him over.
자기 학생한테 어떻게
그럴 수가 있어?
You're this guy's teacher.
How could you do this?
걘 진짜 잘했고, 난 그 역할
정말 정말 하고 싶단 말야
Because the guy's so good.
And I really, really want this part.
Well, if you really, really want it,
then it's okay.
'정말 정말'이라는데
어쩌겠어?
-Hi, Daddy.
-Baby.
- 오셨어요?
- 그래
- 로스!
- 박사님, 안녕하세요?
Dr. Greene, how are you?
어제 저녁은 잘 먹었네
Thanks for dinner last night.
Thank you for teaching me
a valuable lesson.
훌륭한 가르침 감사했습니다
Nice hair. What did you do, swim here?
스타일 좋구만
여기 헤엄쳐서 왔나?
That's it.
I can't take it anymore.
이제 됐어
정말 못해먹겠어
왜? 스타일 좋다시잖아
진짜 궁금해서 물어보신 거야
What? He likes your hair and just
wants to know how you got here.
말이 돼?
- 소용없어, 그냥 갈래
- 뭐? 로스...
-It's hopeless. I'm just gonna go.
-What?
- 미안해, 아무래도...
- 로스!
-I'm sorry. It's just
-Ross?
What's with the neck?
목에 문제 있나?
제 주치의 소개시켜준대도
싫대요
I keep telling him
to go to my chiropractor.
- 너 아직도 거기 다니니?
- 네
You still going to him?
그 놈 돌팔이라고
몇 번을 얘기해?
He couldn't get into
med school in lxtapa!
Thank you.
That's what I keep saying.
저도 맨날 얘기하죠
Excuse me, Dr. Bobby happens
to be an excellent doctor.
잠깐만요
바비 박사는
아주 훌륭한 의사야
Wait a minute.
His name is Dr. Bobby?
잠깐, 이름이 닥터 바비야?
- 네, 성이 바비예요
- 이름도 바비구요
-That's his last name.
-And his first name.
He's Bobby Bobby?
그럼 '바비 바비'네
It's Robert Bobby.
'로버트 바비'예요
그리고 절 치료해주죠
And excuse me. He helps me.
-Please. Ask her how?
-What do you need help for?
- 어떤 치료인지 물어보세요
- 뭘 치료하는데?
My alignment.
One leg's shorter than the other.
교정이요
한 쪽 다리가 짧거든요
- 세상에!
- 말이 안 통하죠
-Oh, my God.
-Argue with that.
My right leg is two inches shorter!
진짜란 말야
오른쪽이 2인치 짧다구
비뚤게 섰잖아!
Come on, you're just tilting!
-Her legs are fine.
-I know that.
- 멀쩡한 걸 갖고
- 저도 알아요
- 알면서도 계속 놔둬?
- '놔둬'라뇨?
-So why do you let her go to him?
-"Let her"?
제 말은 듣지도 않아요
세입자 보험도 안 들었다니까요
She doesn't listen to me
about renter's insurance, either.
세입자 보험 안 들었니?
Wait a minute. You don't have
renter's insurance?
네
How you gonna run after a thief,
with one leg shorter than the other?
도둑이라도 들면 어쩌려고?
짝다리로 어떻게 쫓아가나?
-Would you like some juice?
-I'd love some juice.
- 주스라도 드실래요?
- 주스 좋지
This is going so well!
Did you see us? Did you see?
술술 풀려가는데
- 봤지? 봤어?
- 그럼 못 봤을까봐?
Yeah, honey. I was standing
right there.
Why don't you tell him about
my mole?
사마귀 검진 안 한
얘기도 하시지?
Excellent!
좋았어
There will come a time
in each of your careers...
여러분한테도 경쟁 연기자를
...when you'll have a chance to screw
over another soap opera actor.
속여야 하는 상황이
생길 수 있을 겁니다
I had such an opportunity
in the recent present.
전 최근에
그런 상황을 겪었어요
And I'm ashamed to say...
부끄러운 일이지만
저지르고 말았죠
...that I took it.
I advised a fellow actor
to play a role...
전 그 연기자한테
이렇게 조언했답니다
... homosexually.
동성애자 연기를 해라
우린 같이 오디션을 봤고
We both auditioned for the part...
그리고 결과는...
...and as it turned out...
...they....
게이 연기가 좋다며
그를 뽑았어요
They liked the stupid "gay" thing
and cast him.
And now...
그는 2년 계약을 맺었고
상대역은...
... he's got a two-year contract...
...opposite Susan Lucci...
낮 시간 TV를 주름잡는
수잔 루치라구요
...the first lady
of daytime television.
And me?
근데 난...
Me, I'm stuck here teaching
a bunch of people...
연기 수업을 한답시고
여러분들 앞에 앉았는데
... most of whom are too ugly
to even be on TV.
못생겨서 TV엔 나올 일
없는 학생들이 대부분이에요
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
미안해요
고마워요
Thank you.
침대의 왕 가구점
-May I help you?
-Yes, hi.
- 뭘 도와드릴까요?
- 안녕하세요?
I'm the lady who got stuck
with the racecar bed.
경주차 침대 교환 건으로
전화드렸었죠
Look, it's like I told you.
There's nothing I can do.
이미 말씀드렸다시피
어쩔 수 없습니다
You signed for it.
"Monica Felula Geller."
사인을 하셨잖아요
모니카 벌룰라 겔러 양
All right, we wanna see the King.
광대 양반, 그럼
왕을 만나겠어요
아무도 왕은 못 만나요
Nobody sees the King.
Okay. I'm talking to the King.
만나서 얘기한다니까
Hey, you can't go back there!
거긴 가면 안 돼요
오... 이런... 세상에
Oh, my God.
잘 보고 다녀요!
Hey, watch it, lady!
예쁜데!
Hey, good-looking.
알았어, 갈게
All right, I'll leave.
내 침대는 너무 시시해
My bed's so boring.